Today we are seeing a boom in insurance stocks.
New India Insurance is doing well.
SBI Life is
also doing well. We did see an initial rally in SDFC Life, but
this stock is now trading at a slight decline. Do
you see any opportunities in insurance?
Prashant
ji. Ah, Prashant is not with us. Let's
take a fundamental view on this.
Regarding the insurance space, Gorang sir, are you
looking at the insurance pace and do you
think that a big rally can happen in any stock
or if someone
wants moderate returns, then he can focus and move ahead. It
depends on
which direction you want to go in the insurance sector, whether you want to go towards life insurance
companies
or general insurance.
And we feel that one company,
as far as general insurance is concerned, has a very
good performance and it is not discussed much, that is
ICICI Lombard. From
this perspective also, we have a buy opinion
on ICICI Lombard for the long term. And as far as
your question is about life insurance
companies, here we have seen some change
in the last two months or one month, especially
after the first day's results, it is for the
better.  We have observed
and are making estimates and assessments that
from the 10th or 12th of next month, I think the
results of the second quarter of this
year will start coming in. So, perhaps the improvement may pick up pace.
In the life insurance companies, where there
is LIC, SBI Life, IC
Prudential and HDFC Life, these are the
four companies related to life insurance
where there is a buy opinion and in non-life
general insurance, ICICI
Lombard is fine.
You are also advised to focus on ICC Lombard shares. Let's check some more
shares and one stock
which has a good idea. In the meantime, look at the idea.
This stock will be seen trading at around 10%, going up at around 10%. I
need a review from you in banking once again. Aditya, today
we are seeing that SBI has
moved at around 10% and it is among the top gainers of Nifty. Have
private banks moved too much? Maybe they will go
sideways. Could there be an
opportunity in SBI from this level?
Yes, I also feel that private
sector banks have outperformed a bit
in the last few weeks and meanwhile, PSUs
Banks have underperformed a bit,
so catch-up play should definitely happen now. Let
us see Kotak Bank, Axis Bank and Aaaa
Bank all did very well, meanwhile PNB and
SBI both were underperforming
and today a momentum is visible in all these
PSU banks, so
I definitely feel that SBI can give a good buying
opportunity here. Buying advice would be
above 797. If the
stock trades consistently above that, then a fresh entry should be
taken for the target of 830. At Karan
levels, the stock which I feel is
ready for buying is Cand Bank.
Good momentum is building up here and
I feel that we can buy Cand Bank at the current levels. The
first target on the upper side here will be 112. If it
crosses above that, then the target will be 100. So
buy for the targets of 112 and 115.
Canara should be bought at the current levels and you should place a stop loss of 104 below it
with a stop loss of 104.
You can buy Canara Bank for a target of 1115.
We are seeing a selective move in tyre stocks today,
but CA is up around 1.
MRF is also bullish. Despite being a large-sized
stock, it is bullish around 1.
Alo tyres, which were consistently recommended by our experts
last week, are
also strong. Shivangi, what do
you think is better in tyres? If you want to take a trade, what is the
right thing to do? On technical parameters,
we are seeing a good amount of strength in the auto space. In fact, if
we look at the tyre space, I still believe
that it is in a consolidated mode, so I will keep a little wait
and watch here. Of
course, there is some increase, but my interest
is more in the auto space, so we
can look at some stocks like Bajaj Auto.
These stocks seem to be quite positive.
Bajaj Auto is looking positive. Today, if you
look at aviation, Inter Globe
Aviation is up at 1. Our
experts also had a bullish view on it, and Spice
Jet  Today we are again seeing that
interest has come in, this stock is trading at around 5.
Gorang Sir, I would like to know from you, please
give your view because look, there are two
sectors where
people have understood which is the best
stock. If you talk about aviation, then
people have understood that no, no, Interglobe
is better. If you talk about telecom, then
people have understood that no, no, if you have to choose one stock, then
Vodafone-Idea should be
ahead.
Look Abhishek, in both the sectors
that you mentioned, aviation and
telecom, first of all understand that
in both these sectors, you have to
invest a huge amount of working capital.
These are capital intensive businesses,
you have to continuously upgrade
your
technology, platforms and
infrastructure as far as telecom services are concerned. And as far as aviation is
concerned, you have to repair your aircraft.
And for aviation sector,
it is essential that their aircraft should
remain in the air as much as possible and not on the ground
because if it remains on the ground, it
becomes an overhead cost burden and if it
remains in the air, it increases the income. So now
Spice  There's no coverage on debt, but
if I use my common sense
and fundamental logic to
invest, and if you also have a long-term
perspective, then I think
InterGlobe Aviation Indigo. Firstly, this low-
cost carrier model is just for the name sake. The
flight ticket is similar to a full-flight, full-
service carrier. There's no
difference. Secondly, they are continuously
expanding their fleet of airlines.
You might have heard a few months ago that they placed a
large order for the
aircraft that are grounded due to some technical reasons.
If they are added very soon, the
operating efficiency will increase further. The
way new airports are going to open, as
I was talking to Srishti some time ago,
it will get the biggest benefit
because it is the largest airline
and the management itself has said that
in the coming years they are trying to become an international level
airline. So,
if I had to choose one airline, it would be
InterGlobe Vision. And as I asked Srishti
before the program started on Waff Idea,
I think you asked Srishti about it, so
at 103...  If it was below the FPO price then it
is very much liked and now it is
around 2.5 but keep in mind that
you will have to keep a time horizon of two to two and a half to three years to
improve the situation and it will be
essential to see how the management has
come to the market and raised capital because to
reduce the debt and keep yourself viable
you will have to make continuous efforts.
We had also taken the opinion of Gaurang ji, you
see, the price at 10 is currently strong and
he also told his view on the aviation counter
but in the meantime you see Nifty has
become the top gainer,
today's calls of Divi's Lap and Aditya are going super hit
because see, Nifty is the top gainer, the
rise at 2 is here and along with that
I was also seeing that DLF is also trading at the day high.